<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>youtube on </title>
    <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/youtube/</link>
    <description>Recent content in youtube on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:46:49 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/youtube/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Activity &amp; Creativity. Reflection 14, 15 - Handstand</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/handstand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:46:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/handstand/</guid>
      <description>Reason In the description, I mentioned that I&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting with handstands. It&amp;rsquo;s something I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to learn, and now I&amp;rsquo;m finally giving it a try. While some consider it risky, I disagree. The worst-case scenario is I might go into the bridge position or perform a reverse somersault. So, no need to worry—I&amp;rsquo;ll be just fine.
On another note, I see this as a way to breathe new life into my YouTube channel, which had been inactive for about half a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ativity &amp; Creativity. Reflection 6 &amp; 6 - Around The World</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/running-yt-channel-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 07:52:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/running-yt-channel-p2/</guid>
      <description>Video reflection Since it&amp;rsquo;s about my YouTube channel, I decided to make a video reflection. I talk about what&amp;rsquo;s new in term of the &amp;ldquo;Around The World And Further&amp;rdquo; series. I focus mainly on the technical aspect of editing and numbers those videos make, but I also pay much attention to the football progress. Here it is:
Around The World #5 The second latest video:
Around The World #6 Tha latest video:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Has Just Come Back!</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/start-podcast-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 07:48:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/start-podcast-project/</guid>
      <description>Intro Brief info Welcome in another episode!
We haven&amp;rsquo;t talked for a while, but we&amp;rsquo;re back! Today&amp;rsquo;s podcast is a mock one. We feature another co-speaker, Filip, who will stay with us. The topics covered revolve around the World Cup 2022. We talked mostly about Argentina, Messi and Maradona. We also discussed the tense atmosphere around Polish National Team. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll find something interesting!
Topics covered New co-anchor About the podcast World Cup 2022 Argentina as a winner Messi and Maradona Cultural differences and Messi&amp;rsquo;s background Controversy around Polish National Team Michniewicz and bribery The role of journalism Football and money Success and time A possible Michniewicz&amp;rsquo;s successor To sum up&amp;hellip; Closing thoughts and goodbye Podcast episode Fast goodbye You&amp;rsquo;re up to date by now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity &amp; Creativity. Reflection 5|4 - School Art Festival</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/school-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 08:03:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/school-festival/</guid>
      <description>School Art Festival School Art Festival was quite a journey. In the video below you can learn more about how it was done, why I participated, and what is my opinion. Enjoy!
Christmas Cards As mentioned in the video, in between performances, we could make Christmas cards for Hospicjum Palium in Poznań. I believe it was a great initiative by the organizers. Besides, I really enjoyed making these cards. Here is a taste of how it looked like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity/Activity. Reflection 3/4 - Around the world and further</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/football-choreography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 10:42:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/football-choreography/</guid>
      <description>Video reflection Since this reflection was also about my Youtube channel, I decided to record me relfecting on what I did and how I felt about it.
First video in series Video below is a game changer in terms of my channel. Although I have already released a longer and more complex video, it it this clip that has changed the course of my channel.
Second video in series By creating the successor of the first video, I aimed to add some more humor and fancy editing magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity. Reflection 1 - Running youtube channel</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/running-youtube-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 14:54:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/running-youtube-channel/</guid>
      <description>Me as a youtuber &amp;amp; following thoughts Some channel statistics Overview statistics. There are more views than expected.
Learning outcomes: LO 2 Challenge and Skills LO 3 Initiative and Planning LO 4 Commitment and Perseverance LO 6 Global Engagement </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The channel has kicked off!</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/start-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 16:31:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/start-youtube/</guid>
      <description>My youtube channel has just started! Well, maybe not so recently, but still - there it is and it waits to be discovered by you! There are already some videos (can be viewed also on other pages of this website). Nothing special, but the purpose is to share a bit of my life and the goal is being achieved (gradually)!
What shall these pieces cover? Basically, it&amp;rsquo;s everything I do in my life and is worth reporting somehow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming and Creativity</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 15:10:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/creativity/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my programming and creativity section! Here, you can find out more about my creative pursuits. I describe the history of each of my activities—specifically, programming, juggling, and YouTue—and direct you to places where you can explore even more!
By the way, the dinosaur on the cover is a digital painting by a close friend of mine. Enjoy! ;)
Coding History &amp;amp; Philosophy My passion for programming began in 6th grade when I disassembled an old laptop, which sparked my initial interest in hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
