<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>workout on </title>
    <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/workout/</link>
    <description>Recent content in workout on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:46:49 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/workout/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Activity &amp; Creativity. Reflection 14, 15 - Handstand</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/handstand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:46:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/handstand/</guid>
      <description>Reason In the description, I mentioned that I&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting with handstands. It&amp;rsquo;s something I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to learn, and now I&amp;rsquo;m finally giving it a try. While some consider it risky, I disagree. The worst-case scenario is I might go into the bridge position or perform a reverse somersault. So, no need to worry—I&amp;rsquo;ll be just fine.
On another note, I see this as a way to breathe new life into my YouTube channel, which had been inactive for about half a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity. Reflection 12 - Wood Splitting</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/wood-splitting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:34:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/wood-splitting/</guid>
      <description>The need The description may be misleading because I don&amp;rsquo;t mind when it&amp;rsquo;s freezing and, on the contrary, I actually enjoy it. However, I&amp;rsquo;m an exception so a certain level of temperature must be maintained using the fireplace which, in our case, is powered with wood. Unfortunately, the wood comes in big slices that can&amp;rsquo;t quite fit and some adjustments need to be made. This is the reason why I was employed in wood splitting - to make the wood smaller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity. Reflection 11 - Painting Fence</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/painting-fence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 19:14:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/painting-fence/</guid>
      <description>Ridiculousness Normally, I would report something about stretching, a new exercise, or football. However, painting my fence took me so long and exhausted so much that I barely had strength to do anything else. So I thought to myself &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s stopping me from reflecting on this? NOTHING&amp;rdquo; (beside the fact that my brother was the one to whom the task was initially assigned, but he needed some proper motivation it turned out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity. Reflection 10 - July Activity</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/july-activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:07:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/july-activity/</guid>
      <description>Little darlin&amp;rsquo;, I feel that ice is slowly melting Little darlin&amp;rsquo;, it seems like years since it&amp;rsquo;s been clear
The Beatles, &amp;ldquo;Here Comes The Sun&amp;rdquo; Hello world! Although I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t call myself a summer lover, I must admit that summer opens up the door for a considerable number of activities that are less available or less pleasant during the rest of the year. In addition, summer means vacation, which, supposedly, translates to a huge amount of free time (unless you&amp;rsquo;re an IB student.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service/Activity. Reflection 3 - Meeting with my charges</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/meeting-charges/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 07:55:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/meeting-charges/</guid>
      <description>A glimpse into my work I regularly meet with all my &amp;ldquo;Bears&amp;rdquo;1 from the camp - Piotr, Marcin, and Adam. Since there are three of them, I visit each tri-weekly (usually). This is also due to logistic reasons. They live all across Poznań. Commuting unavoidably consumes much of my time and, although I get to know new places (like a cozy café in Wilda district!) which is fine, sadly I can&amp;rsquo;t pay them visits more often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 15:10:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/activity/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my activity section! Here, I will introduce everything I do as a physical exercise. This includes: football, workout and stretching.
Football Description: My journey with football isn&amp;rsquo;t so straightforward. I started hating it, but ended up loving it. Now it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to wind down and make friendships! By the way, my position is a goalkeeper and favourite club is Manchester United.
In 2019 our team went to Denmark.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
