<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>temporary-events on </title>
    <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/temporary-events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in temporary-events on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 18:47:08 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/temporary-events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 15 - Poznański Wolontariusz Roku</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/poznanski-wolontariusz-roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 18:47:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/poznanski-wolontariusz-roku/</guid>
      <description>Poznański Wolontariusz Roku Poznański Wolontariusz Roku (Poznań Volunteer of the Year) is an annual competition that recognizes and rewards individuals who dedicate a significant portion of their lives to volunteer work. The laureates are chosen by the competition jury and fall into six categories:
Youth: for individuals below the age of 19 Individual: for individuals between the ages of 19 and 60 Senior: for individuals above the age of 60 Group: for groups conducting volunteer activities School Volunteering: for teams operating within school volunteer circles Employee Volunteering: for employee volunteering programs I was, of course, in the first group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service &amp; Creativity. Reflection 8 &amp; 9 - Sault Dough Workshops</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/bury-mis-salt-dough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 15:01:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/bury-mis-salt-dough/</guid>
      <description>The crew and the plan Every good plan starts with a good idea and a reliable crew, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it? The salt dough workshops began exactly like this. It was an ordinary winter day (winter because of the month, not the weather) that a fellow volunteer came up with a thought of crafting something original for Świętnica at Osada, Kaszuby, which ends the holidays. Another individual suggested salt dough for this noble cause as it is one of these kids-love-playing-with magical substances that leaves a lot of space for imagination (and mess naturally, but who cares?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Relfection 7 - Drużyna Szpiku</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/druzyna-szpiku/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 07:28:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/druzyna-szpiku/</guid>
      <description>def change_the_world(persistence: bool, goodwill: bool, knowledge: bool): &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34;To be rembered forever&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; if not persistence: raise FallDownError if not goodwill: raise CrueltyError if not knowledge: raise AwarenessError return make_change(persistence, goodwill, knowledge) Drużyna Szpiku The trigger for the inception of Drużyna Szpiku1 in 2008 was Anna Wierska who, struggling with blood cancer and the lack of donor by herself, aimed to help other afflicted people by raising awareness about the importance of blood donation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 4 - X-MAS Cup 2022 🎅⚽</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/football-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 12:31:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/football-competition/</guid>
      <description>What on earth is going on? Christmas&amp;hellip; WHAT?! X-MAS cup 2022 was a tournament for all young players from Lech Poznań Football Academies (LFPA) no matter where they were located1. The director of LFPA, Dominik Czapczyk, describes this series of events as follows:
&amp;ldquo;Annual X-MAS Cups are both a big thank-you to LFPA players for their hard work and place to simply hang out.&amp;rdquo; 🎅 ⚽
As you can see, the underlying aim was priceless; at the end of the day, what values the most is a child&amp;rsquo;s smile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 2 - Organizing Pomocna Piątka run</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/pomocna-piatka-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 07:24:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/pomocna-piatka-organization/</guid>
      <description>What a day it was! After spending a marvelous night at a gig dedicated to Pink Floyd history with my grandpa, brother and friend, I had to wake up at 5:00a.m.! This is because I decided to reach the destination by bike. Compared to a combustion-engine-powered car or bus, a bike is arguably the most eco-friendly means of transport (and considerably less outside-world-dependent) hence my choice. Nonetheless, there were nearly 20km to be travelled and no time to be wasted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 1 - Preparing for PoMocna Piątka run</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/pomocna-piatka-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 13:04:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/pomocna-piatka-preparation/</guid>
      <description>To begin with, everything started at the end of the previous school year (2021-2022). Our, current CAS coordinator, then English teacher, asked us if we would like to participate in an event, called PoMocna Piątka run. Some of us where keen to sign up, including me.
Next school year (2022-2023) we were reminded of that list and that event and asked to confirm our choice. I turned out to be the first student to do so, therefore, I was asked to coordinate the whole operation at our school (GeS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 15:11:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/service/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my servie section Here, I will present everything I do voluntarily, serving others. This includes: the foundation of Bury Miś, teaching and temporary events.
Bury Miś Description: The foundation of Bury Miś is a charity, aiming to help disabled people - both physically and intelectually. The charity was found in 1983 in Cracow, but moved to Nowy Klincz 9 years later. My contribution here is serving as a counselor during camps organized for the disabled, meeting with my charges throughout the year and occasionally selling hand-made Kashubian chesse.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
