<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>creativity on </title>
    <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/creativity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in creativity on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 08:37:08 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/creativity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Revival and updates #0</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/revival-and-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 08:37:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/revival-and-updates/</guid>
      <description>A Few Words of Explanation If you&amp;rsquo;ve been following my posts, you might have noticed a pattern of increasingly long breaks, especially since the second half of 2023. But a 7-month gap? That’s by far the longest pause yet (my last post, dated here, was that long ago).
Originally, this post was meant to mark my blog’s revival in the fall of 2024. At the time, I had written an opening about my increasingly long breaks—especially the seven-month gap (see above) since my last post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAS - Final Reflection</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/cas-final-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:40:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/cas-final-reflection/</guid>
      <description>Prelude It&amp;rsquo;s fascinating to look back on the creation of this portfolio. I remember the days at the Bury Mis camp, waking up early to work on this site in peace. The struggle with understanding Hugo&amp;rsquo;s folder structure, now trivial, was so daunting back then. Even after the summer of 2022, I still hadn&amp;rsquo;t figured out all the inner workings, like how to place pictures side by side. I felt the weight of my promise to finish my CAS portfolio by the start of my junior year, and the pressure was intense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 19, 18 - IBlieve #4</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:32:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-4/</guid>
      <description>Back to the past Recall from the previous blog entry on IBlieve that my article on IB&amp;rsquo;s Middle Years Programme was not yet published. Well, that has changed! You can now see the cover and first paragraph of this article in the cover of this post. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested, you can also read the full article on IBlieve.
Now, more importantly, I&amp;rsquo;m back from my break, fully dedicated to finishing my IBDP work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity. Reflection 18 - Valentine&#39;s Painting</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/valentines-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 10:40:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/valentines-painting/</guid>
      <description>Heated debate The atmosphere during Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day contrasts with the hustle and stress often associated with holidays like Christmas. While Christmas can be hectic with many people rushing around, Valentine&amp;rsquo;s tends to bring a sense of relief as couples focus on each other&amp;rsquo;s happiness rather than external pressures like politics or economics.
Although this perspective isn&amp;rsquo;t based on extensive research and individual experiences may vary, it reflects a different attitude towards Valentine&amp;rsquo;s compared to other holidays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity. Reflection 17 - Resource Center #3</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/resource-center-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 17:18:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/resource-center-3/</guid>
      <description>EE, my struggle The word &amp;lsquo;struggle&amp;rsquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t quite fit, but it is eye-catching, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? I mean, it embodies the truth to a limited degree, but it&amp;rsquo;s a bit of an exaggeration. Why? Because I&amp;rsquo;m referring to my process of writing the Extended Essay in Computer Science, which was challenging and, at the same time, really got me going. I chose the right subject and an up-to-date area of research, namely Artificial Intelligence, broadly speaking, of course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 16, 16 - IBlieve #3</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 10:48:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-3/</guid>
      <description>A memory refresher The last time I shared updates on my IBlieve journey was a year ago&amp;hellip; according to calendar because actually it was two months ago, in the first half of November, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist a New Year joke. Anyway, such a large time gap can negatively affect our memory, so let&amp;rsquo;s quickly revisit what I discussed previously.
The last blog post on my involvement in IBlieve featured a huge section on unpublished articles, all of which are now published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity &amp; Creativity. Reflection 14, 15 - Handstand</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/handstand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:46:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/handstand/</guid>
      <description>Reason In the description, I mentioned that I&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting with handstands. It&amp;rsquo;s something I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to learn, and now I&amp;rsquo;m finally giving it a try. While some consider it risky, I disagree. The worst-case scenario is I might go into the bridge position or perform a reverse somersault. So, no need to worry—I&amp;rsquo;ll be just fine.
On another note, I see this as a way to breathe new life into my YouTube channel, which had been inactive for about half a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 14, 14 - IBlieve #2</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 07:29:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-2/</guid>
      <description>Focus I believe it&amp;rsquo;s pointless to repeat over and over again what IBlieve is and what my role entails. I explained all essentials here. So let&amp;rsquo;s jump straight to the work I did.
CAS 101 This article is a bit of an exception because it is not an article as such, but an interview. The story is, I was assigned the following topic: &amp;ldquo;Do&amp;rsquo;s and Don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rsquo;s for CAS&amp;rdquo;. However, I had no idea whatsoever how to approach it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 13, 12 - IBlieve</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:34:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve/</guid>
      <description>IBlieve In a blog posts I wrote a while ago, I mentioned I applied to IBlieve - a volunteer organization that helps students to learn. I said that I would create a breakdown of the curriculum of computer science course if I would get accepted. Well, I did get accepted, but I chose different topics, but what exactly? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out!
Benefits for IB students in the US The first article was titled &amp;ldquo;Benfefits for IB students in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity. Reflection 12 - IT Internship</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/it-internship/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 16:50:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/it-internship/</guid>
      <description>A word or two of intro As you might suspect, neither the title nor the cover are sufficient to fully describe the whole situation. Moreover, not only are they not enough, but more importantly, they are misleading because technology is a vast ocean that is both dangerous and fascinating. Therefore, one cannot encapsulate its essence in a mere picture or a few words. But putting the geeky talking aside, some explanation is required to give a big picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Activity &amp; Service. Reflection 11, 9, 10 - Group Reflection</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/group-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 15:29:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/group-reflection/</guid>
      <description>The Story The story behind this post is simple. Today, we had our last CAS lesson this school year and our dear coordinator wanted us to create a group reflection. We were given (giant) pieces of paper on which learning outcomes were written for us to describe what we did over the year to meet these learning outcomes.
Each of us (the handful that showed up) along with the coordinator wrote a short note, explaining our actions within every learning outcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity. Reflection 10 - Resource Center #2</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/resource-center-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 18:12:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/resource-center-2/</guid>
      <description>Overview The last update concerning the Resource Center dates back to the beginning of 2023 when I introduced the project, explained what I added, and proposed some future developments. If you have no clue of what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about or you need to refresh your memory, please feel free to open the previous post. However, if you do not have time or patience to do so, no worries, what I&amp;rsquo;m about to discuss is rather straightforward and context-independent, at least to some degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAS Project - School Interior Design</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/interior-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 15:11:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/interior-design/</guid>
      <description>My imagination is more vivid than life.
50 cent Project outline Category Description Project title School Interior Design Project leader Cecilia Ontañón Berganza Members Cecilia Ontañón Berganza, Jagoda Lipowicz, Mateusz Konat, Jan Babiarz, Amelia Kamińska Focus of the project The decoration of the school building for various occasions Supervisor Aleksandra Sobala-Woźniak Anticipated dates Throught the 2022-2023 school year IPARD Investigation September 2023 There was a widespread complain about the school building&amp;rsquo;s design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service &amp; Creativity. Reflection 8 &amp; 9 - Sault Dough Workshops</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/bury-mis-salt-dough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 15:01:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/bury-mis-salt-dough/</guid>
      <description>The crew and the plan Every good plan starts with a good idea and a reliable crew, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it? The salt dough workshops began exactly like this. It was an ordinary winter day (winter because of the month, not the weather) that a fellow volunteer came up with a thought of crafting something original for Świętnica at Osada, Kaszuby, which ends the holidays. Another individual suggested salt dough for this noble cause as it is one of these kids-love-playing-with magical substances that leaves a lot of space for imagination (and mess naturally, but who cares?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity. Reflection 8 - CSV SQLite Converter</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/csv-sqlite-converter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 07:11:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/csv-sqlite-converter/</guid>
      <description>Open source culture Obsession can often get things done.
John Carmack1 Here is a brilliant video that explains the philosophy of open source culture:
It highlights two most important aspects of open source:
It is available for everyone Together, we can make it better The idea of creating a useful code with others appeals to many programmers and pushes them toward open-sourcing their own code to be improved with external help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ativity &amp; Creativity. Reflection 7 &amp; 7 - Shorts</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/youtube-shorts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 18:16:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/youtube-shorts/</guid>
      <description>Video reflection My channel was&amp;hellip; standing idle for quite a time. However, here I am once again to talk with pleasure to you! Today, I discussed YouTube Shorts section of my channel since I haven&amp;rsquo;t done it yet. Never. So it was the high time to do so. Have a seat, make yourself comfortable and watch!
Short #3 The second latest video:
Short #4 Tha latest video:
Learning outcomes: LO 1 Strength and Growth LO 2 Challenge and Skills LO 3 Initiative and Planning LO 4 Commitment and Perseverance LO 5 Collaborative Skills LO 6 Global Engagement LO 7 Ethics of Choices and Actions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ativity &amp; Creativity. Reflection 6 &amp; 6 - Around The World</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/running-yt-channel-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 07:52:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/running-yt-channel-p2/</guid>
      <description>Video reflection Since it&amp;rsquo;s about my YouTube channel, I decided to make a video reflection. I talk about what&amp;rsquo;s new in term of the &amp;ldquo;Around The World And Further&amp;rdquo; series. I focus mainly on the technical aspect of editing and numbers those videos make, but I also pay much attention to the football progress. Here it is:
Around The World #5 The second latest video:
Around The World #6 Tha latest video:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity. Reflection 5 - Com. Sci. Resource Center</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/resource-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 09:18:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/resource-center/</guid>
      <description>What is this project about? The project is called Computer Science Resource Center (we&amp;rsquo;re working on something more subtle). As you may infer from the name, it&amp;rsquo;s dedicated to computer science, specifically to IBDP CS course. You can find there a decent overview of the course, including things like: grade boundaries, resources, the description of each assessment component, and the latest news.
Initially, the website was created by Mr. Bartłomiej Przybylski to enhance communication between him and students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Has Just Come Back!</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/start-podcast-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 07:48:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/start-podcast-project/</guid>
      <description>Intro Brief info Welcome in another episode!
We haven&amp;rsquo;t talked for a while, but we&amp;rsquo;re back! Today&amp;rsquo;s podcast is a mock one. We feature another co-speaker, Filip, who will stay with us. The topics covered revolve around the World Cup 2022. We talked mostly about Argentina, Messi and Maradona. We also discussed the tense atmosphere around Polish National Team. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll find something interesting!
Topics covered New co-anchor About the podcast World Cup 2022 Argentina as a winner Messi and Maradona Cultural differences and Messi&amp;rsquo;s background Controversy around Polish National Team Michniewicz and bribery The role of journalism Football and money Success and time A possible Michniewicz&amp;rsquo;s successor To sum up&amp;hellip; Closing thoughts and goodbye Podcast episode Fast goodbye You&amp;rsquo;re up to date by now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity &amp; Creativity. Reflection 5|4 - School Art Festival</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/school-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 08:03:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/school-festival/</guid>
      <description>School Art Festival School Art Festival was quite a journey. In the video below you can learn more about how it was done, why I participated, and what is my opinion. Enjoy!
Christmas Cards As mentioned in the video, in between performances, we could make Christmas cards for Hospicjum Palium in Poznań. I believe it was a great initiative by the organizers. Besides, I really enjoyed making these cards. Here is a taste of how it looked like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity/Activity. Reflection 3/4 - Around the world and further</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/football-choreography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 10:42:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/football-choreography/</guid>
      <description>Video reflection Since this reflection was also about my Youtube channel, I decided to record me relfecting on what I did and how I felt about it.
First video in series Video below is a game changer in terms of my channel. Although I have already released a longer and more complex video, it it this clip that has changed the course of my channel.
Second video in series By creating the successor of the first video, I aimed to add some more humor and fancy editing magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity. Reflection 2 -  Refactoring CAS Manager</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/cas-manager-refactoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 08:03:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/cas-manager-refactoring/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER The version of the program I talk about in this blog post concern GitHub history up to this commit. Later, I discovered that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t improve anything with the code that was there. Therefore, I dicided to abandon it and write the program from scratch. Considering the effort I have put into this, I have made it my Computer Science Internal Assessment. As a result, it is no longer part of my CAS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity. Reflection 1 - Running youtube channel</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/running-youtube-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 14:54:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/running-youtube-channel/</guid>
      <description>Me as a youtuber &amp;amp; following thoughts Some channel statistics Overview statistics. There are more views than expected.
Learning outcomes: LO 2 Challenge and Skills LO 3 Initiative and Planning LO 4 Commitment and Perseverance LO 6 Global Engagement </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The channel has kicked off!</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/start-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 16:31:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/start-youtube/</guid>
      <description>My youtube channel has just started! Well, maybe not so recently, but still - there it is and it waits to be discovered by you! There are already some videos (can be viewed also on other pages of this website). Nothing special, but the purpose is to share a bit of my life and the goal is being achieved (gradually)!
What shall these pieces cover? Basically, it&amp;rsquo;s everything I do in my life and is worth reporting somehow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming and Creativity</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 15:10:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/creativity/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my programming and creativity section! Here, you can find out more about my creative pursuits. I describe the history of each of my activities—specifically, programming, juggling, and YouTue—and direct you to places where you can explore even more!
By the way, the dinosaur on the cover is a digital painting by a close friend of mine. Enjoy! ;)
Coding History &amp;amp; Philosophy My passion for programming began in 6th grade when I disassembled an old laptop, which sparked my initial interest in hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 11:41:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/projects/</guid>
      <description>Technology advances when the solution to a particular problem finds a more general application.
Don Eyles1 The idea behind The idea that software should be shared and freely accessible for everyone lies at the core of programming. Sharing software allows individuals to learn from the experience of others, to avoid common mistakes and consequently - to write software faster and better, advancing our understanding of the world. Therefore, I, allowing others to learn and learning by myself, want to share my Github with those interested in changing our lives!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 11:38:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello World! Welcome to my website! I&amp;rsquo;m Mateusz Konat, a passionate tech tinkerer eager to share my journey with you.
Here, you&amp;rsquo;ll discover more about me and my activities, explore my blog, and dive into my projects.
Also, you can easily navigate through the content of interest on my website using the tags at the top of each page (indicated by &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; sign like &amp;ldquo;#my projects&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;#creativity&amp;rdquo;).
Now, let me tell you more about myself!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
