<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>football on </title>
    <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/football/</link>
    <description>Recent content in football on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 07:52:23 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/football/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ativity &amp; Creativity. Reflection 6 &amp; 6 - Around The World</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/running-yt-channel-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 07:52:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/running-yt-channel-p2/</guid>
      <description>Video reflection Since it&amp;rsquo;s about my YouTube channel, I decided to make a video reflection. I talk about what&amp;rsquo;s new in term of the &amp;ldquo;Around The World And Further&amp;rdquo; series. I focus mainly on the technical aspect of editing and numbers those videos make, but I also pay much attention to the football progress. Here it is:
Around The World #5 The second latest video:
Around The World #6 Tha latest video:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity/Activity. Reflection 3/4 - Around the world and further</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/football-choreography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 10:42:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/football-choreography/</guid>
      <description>Video reflection Since this reflection was also about my Youtube channel, I decided to record me relfecting on what I did and how I felt about it.
First video in series Video below is a game changer in terms of my channel. Although I have already released a longer and more complex video, it it this clip that has changed the course of my channel.
Second video in series By creating the successor of the first video, I aimed to add some more humor and fancy editing magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity. Reflection 2 - Steady head</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/steady-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 13:33:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/steady-head/</guid>
      <description>How did I start? I find it worth-mentioning, the beginnings. Why? Because it started when I was &amp;ldquo;pursuing my football dreams&amp;rdquo;. More specifically, when we (my team at that time) had the header exam. To pass, we had to hit the ball with your head 15 times (additional 16th hit was for a higher mark). As simple as that, right? No, if you have never juggled with your head! And this was my case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 15:10:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/activity/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my activity section! Here, I will introduce everything I do as a physical exercise. This includes: football, workout and stretching.
Football Description: My journey with football isn&amp;rsquo;t so straightforward. I started hating it, but ended up loving it. Now it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to wind down and make friendships! By the way, my position is a goalkeeper and favourite club is Manchester United.
In 2019 our team went to Denmark.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
