<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>writing on </title>
    <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in writing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:32:19 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 19, 18 - IBlieve #4</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:32:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-4/</guid>
      <description>Back to the past Recall from the previous blog entry on IBlieve that my article on IB&amp;rsquo;s Middle Years Programme was not yet published. Well, that has changed! You can now see the cover and first paragraph of this article in the cover of this post. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested, you can also read the full article on IBlieve.
Now, more importantly, I&amp;rsquo;m back from my break, fully dedicated to finishing my IBDP work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 16, 16 - IBlieve #3</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 10:48:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-3/</guid>
      <description>A memory refresher The last time I shared updates on my IBlieve journey was a year ago&amp;hellip; according to calendar because actually it was two months ago, in the first half of November, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist a New Year joke. Anyway, such a large time gap can negatively affect our memory, so let&amp;rsquo;s quickly revisit what I discussed previously.
The last blog post on my involvement in IBlieve featured a huge section on unpublished articles, all of which are now published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 14, 14 - IBlieve #2</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 07:29:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-2/</guid>
      <description>Focus I believe it&amp;rsquo;s pointless to repeat over and over again what IBlieve is and what my role entails. I explained all essentials here. So let&amp;rsquo;s jump straight to the work I did.
CAS 101 This article is a bit of an exception because it is not an article as such, but an interview. The story is, I was assigned the following topic: &amp;ldquo;Do&amp;rsquo;s and Don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rsquo;s for CAS&amp;rdquo;. However, I had no idea whatsoever how to approach it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 13, 12 - IBlieve</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:34:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve/</guid>
      <description>IBlieve In a blog posts I wrote a while ago, I mentioned I applied to IBlieve - a volunteer organization that helps students to learn. I said that I would create a breakdown of the curriculum of computer science course if I would get accepted. Well, I did get accepted, but I chose different topics, but what exactly? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out!
Benefits for IB students in the US The first article was titled &amp;ldquo;Benfefits for IB students in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
