<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>service on </title>
    <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in service on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 08:37:08 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Revival and updates #0</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/revival-and-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 08:37:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/revival-and-updates/</guid>
      <description>A Few Words of Explanation If you&amp;rsquo;ve been following my posts, you might have noticed a pattern of increasingly long breaks, especially since the second half of 2023. But a 7-month gap? That’s by far the longest pause yet (my last post, dated here, was that long ago).
Originally, this post was meant to mark my blog’s revival in the fall of 2024. At the time, I had written an opening about my increasingly long breaks—especially the seven-month gap (see above) since my last post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAS - Final Reflection</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/cas-final-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:40:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/cas-final-reflection/</guid>
      <description>Prelude It&amp;rsquo;s fascinating to look back on the creation of this portfolio. I remember the days at the Bury Mis camp, waking up early to work on this site in peace. The struggle with understanding Hugo&amp;rsquo;s folder structure, now trivial, was so daunting back then. Even after the summer of 2022, I still hadn&amp;rsquo;t figured out all the inner workings, like how to place pictures side by side. I felt the weight of my promise to finish my CAS portfolio by the start of my junior year, and the pressure was intense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 19, 18 - IBlieve #4</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:32:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-4/</guid>
      <description>Back to the past Recall from the previous blog entry on IBlieve that my article on IB&amp;rsquo;s Middle Years Programme was not yet published. Well, that has changed! You can now see the cover and first paragraph of this article in the cover of this post. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested, you can also read the full article on IBlieve.
Now, more importantly, I&amp;rsquo;m back from my break, fully dedicated to finishing my IBDP work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 17 - Meeting Charges p.4</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/meeting-charges-p4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 13:24:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/meeting-charges-p4/</guid>
      <description>Time capsule In the description of this blog post, I emphasized the significance of my interactions with my charges. It might be surprising for those who glance at my portfolio and notice that the last reflection on this topic dates back to October of last year!
While I don&amp;rsquo;t have a groundbreaking explanation, I simply directed my reflections towards other matters during that period, and nothing unusual occurred to prompt a new entry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 16, 16 - IBlieve #3</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 10:48:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-3/</guid>
      <description>A memory refresher The last time I shared updates on my IBlieve journey was a year ago&amp;hellip; according to calendar because actually it was two months ago, in the first half of November, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist a New Year joke. Anyway, such a large time gap can negatively affect our memory, so let&amp;rsquo;s quickly revisit what I discussed previously.
The last blog post on my involvement in IBlieve featured a huge section on unpublished articles, all of which are now published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 15 - Poznański Wolontariusz Roku</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/poznanski-wolontariusz-roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 18:47:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/poznanski-wolontariusz-roku/</guid>
      <description>Poznański Wolontariusz Roku Poznański Wolontariusz Roku (Poznań Volunteer of the Year) is an annual competition that recognizes and rewards individuals who dedicate a significant portion of their lives to volunteer work. The laureates are chosen by the competition jury and fall into six categories:
Youth: for individuals below the age of 19 Individual: for individuals between the ages of 19 and 60 Senior: for individuals above the age of 60 Group: for groups conducting volunteer activities School Volunteering: for teams operating within school volunteer circles Employee Volunteering: for employee volunteering programs I was, of course, in the first group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 14, 14 - IBlieve #2</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 07:29:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve-2/</guid>
      <description>Focus I believe it&amp;rsquo;s pointless to repeat over and over again what IBlieve is and what my role entails. I explained all essentials here. So let&amp;rsquo;s jump straight to the work I did.
CAS 101 This article is a bit of an exception because it is not an article as such, but an interview. The story is, I was assigned the following topic: &amp;ldquo;Do&amp;rsquo;s and Don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rsquo;s for CAS&amp;rdquo;. However, I had no idea whatsoever how to approach it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 13 - Meeting Charges p.3</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/meeting-charges-p3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:52:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/meeting-charges-p3/</guid>
      <description>A simple catch-up As I underlined in the description of this beautiful blog post, an ongoing commitment to an activity earns you respect and trust. In the life of mine, the most resonating and continuous pastime is meeting my lovely charges. Therefore, it is unfortunate that my bulging holiday schedule made those meetings impossible.
Nevertheless, school year has been bringing me to Poznań every day of the workweek, which obviously facilities commuting to my charges and turns me into their frequent visitor - not all of them, much to my disappointment, but more on this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Service. Reflection 13, 12 - IBlieve</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:34:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/iblieve/</guid>
      <description>IBlieve In a blog posts I wrote a while ago, I mentioned I applied to IBlieve - a volunteer organization that helps students to learn. I said that I would create a breakdown of the curriculum of computer science course if I would get accepted. Well, I did get accepted, but I chose different topics, but what exactly? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out!
Benefits for IB students in the US The first article was titled &amp;ldquo;Benfefits for IB students in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 11 - Bury Miś Presentation</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/bury-mis-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 08:05:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/bury-mis-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer The presentation (actually, a series of presentations) I would like to talk about happend at the end end of 2022-2023 school year. Therefore, it begs a question why the report is being written so late? Well, I was simply busy and had no time - at the end of the day part-time job, plus internships consumes a lot of my time.
However, I have finally found a free period in my schedule and I&amp;rsquo;m ready to catch up with the updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity &amp; Activity &amp; Service. Reflection 11, 9, 10 - Group Reflection</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/group-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 15:29:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/group-reflection/</guid>
      <description>The Story The story behind this post is simple. Today, we had our last CAS lesson this school year and our dear coordinator wanted us to create a group reflection. We were given (giant) pieces of paper on which learning outcomes were written for us to describe what we did over the year to meet these learning outcomes.
Each of us (the handful that showed up) along with the coordinator wrote a short note, explaining our actions within every learning outcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 9 - Bury Miś Workshops</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/bury-mis-workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 07:12:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/bury-mis-workshops/</guid>
      <description>Let mercy come and wash away
Linkin Park Before Each time I type these two commands in the Terminal:
&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; hugo new posts/{name_of_reflection}/index.md &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; mkdir content/posts/{name_of_reflection}/images I know I am going to spend next 1 or 2 hours polishing my newly-created blog post. I do not complain, no way! I happily do all I can to deliver the best possible reader experience. I prefer quality over quantity such that I can highlight what is the most important in my reflections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service &amp; Creativity. Reflection 8 &amp; 9 - Sault Dough Workshops</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/bury-mis-salt-dough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 15:01:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/bury-mis-salt-dough/</guid>
      <description>The crew and the plan Every good plan starts with a good idea and a reliable crew, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it? The salt dough workshops began exactly like this. It was an ordinary winter day (winter because of the month, not the weather) that a fellow volunteer came up with a thought of crafting something original for Świętnica at Osada, Kaszuby, which ends the holidays. Another individual suggested salt dough for this noble cause as it is one of these kids-love-playing-with magical substances that leaves a lot of space for imagination (and mess naturally, but who cares?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Relfection 7 - Drużyna Szpiku</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/druzyna-szpiku/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 07:28:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/druzyna-szpiku/</guid>
      <description>def change_the_world(persistence: bool, goodwill: bool, knowledge: bool): &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34;To be rembered forever&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; if not persistence: raise FallDownError if not goodwill: raise CrueltyError if not knowledge: raise AwarenessError return make_change(persistence, goodwill, knowledge) Drużyna Szpiku The trigger for the inception of Drużyna Szpiku1 in 2008 was Anna Wierska who, struggling with blood cancer and the lack of donor by herself, aimed to help other afflicted people by raising awareness about the importance of blood donation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 6 - Meeting Charges p.2</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/meeting-charges-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 12:18:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/meeting-charges-p2/</guid>
      <description>A quick pill of essentials In the past few months, I have participated in a number of new service activities that consumed most of my time devoted to this blog/portfolio. In fact, the last reflection dedicated to my boys (Piotr, Maciej and Adam) dates back to November 2022! As you can see, it&amp;rsquo;s the high time I come back with a refreshed set of experiences and thoughts that have hit me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 5 - Selling Kashubian Cheese</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/selling-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 10:51:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/selling-cheese/</guid>
      <description>A Short Story About Bury Miś And Cheese Seemingly, the Bury Miś Foundation is only a typical organization where enthusiastic volunteers attempt to make life of the disadvantaged more enjoyable. Indeed, it provides social interaction and support to people who are in a strong need of the company of others and struggle to develop bonds with society, which is worthy of admiration. However, what does differ the Bury Miś Foundation from other similar organizations is its complexity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 4 - X-MAS Cup 2022 🎅⚽</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/football-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 12:31:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/football-competition/</guid>
      <description>What on earth is going on? Christmas&amp;hellip; WHAT?! X-MAS cup 2022 was a tournament for all young players from Lech Poznań Football Academies (LFPA) no matter where they were located1. The director of LFPA, Dominik Czapczyk, describes this series of events as follows:
&amp;ldquo;Annual X-MAS Cups are both a big thank-you to LFPA players for their hard work and place to simply hang out.&amp;rdquo; 🎅 ⚽
As you can see, the underlying aim was priceless; at the end of the day, what values the most is a child&amp;rsquo;s smile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service/Activity. Reflection 3 - Meeting with my charges</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/meeting-charges/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 07:55:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/meeting-charges/</guid>
      <description>A glimpse into my work I regularly meet with all my &amp;ldquo;Bears&amp;rdquo;1 from the camp - Piotr, Marcin, and Adam. Since there are three of them, I visit each tri-weekly (usually). This is also due to logistic reasons. They live all across Poznań. Commuting unavoidably consumes much of my time and, although I get to know new places (like a cozy café in Wilda district!) which is fine, sadly I can&amp;rsquo;t pay them visits more often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 2 - Organizing Pomocna Piątka run</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/pomocna-piatka-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 07:24:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/pomocna-piatka-organization/</guid>
      <description>What a day it was! After spending a marvelous night at a gig dedicated to Pink Floyd history with my grandpa, brother and friend, I had to wake up at 5:00a.m.! This is because I decided to reach the destination by bike. Compared to a combustion-engine-powered car or bus, a bike is arguably the most eco-friendly means of transport (and considerably less outside-world-dependent) hence my choice. Nonetheless, there were nearly 20km to be travelled and no time to be wasted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service. Reflection 1 - Preparing for PoMocna Piątka run</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/pomocna-piatka-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 13:04:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/pomocna-piatka-preparation/</guid>
      <description>To begin with, everything started at the end of the previous school year (2021-2022). Our, current CAS coordinator, then English teacher, asked us if we would like to participate in an event, called PoMocna Piątka run. Some of us where keen to sign up, including me.
Next school year (2022-2023) we were reminded of that list and that event and asked to confirm our choice. I turned out to be the first student to do so, therefore, I was asked to coordinate the whole operation at our school (GeS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 15:11:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/service/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my servie section Here, I will present everything I do voluntarily, serving others. This includes: the foundation of Bury Miś, teaching and temporary events.
Bury Miś Description: The foundation of Bury Miś is a charity, aiming to help disabled people - both physically and intelectually. The charity was found in 1983 in Cracow, but moved to Nowy Klincz 9 years later. My contribution here is serving as a counselor during camps organized for the disabled, meeting with my charges throughout the year and occasionally selling hand-made Kashubian chesse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 11:38:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello World! Welcome to my website! I&amp;rsquo;m Mateusz Konat, a passionate tech tinkerer eager to share my journey with you.
Here, you&amp;rsquo;ll discover more about me and my activities, explore my blog, and dive into my projects.
Also, you can easily navigate through the content of interest on my website using the tags at the top of each page (indicated by &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; sign like &amp;ldquo;#my projects&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;#creativity&amp;rdquo;).
Now, let me tell you more about myself!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
