<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cas project on </title>
    <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/cas-project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cas project on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:40:01 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/tags/cas-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CAS - Final Reflection</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/cas-final-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:40:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/cas-final-reflection/</guid>
      <description>Prelude It&amp;rsquo;s fascinating to look back on the creation of this portfolio. I remember the days at the Bury Mis camp, waking up early to work on this site in peace. The struggle with understanding Hugo&amp;rsquo;s folder structure, now trivial, was so daunting back then. Even after the summer of 2022, I still hadn&amp;rsquo;t figured out all the inner workings, like how to place pictures side by side. I felt the weight of my promise to finish my CAS portfolio by the start of my junior year, and the pressure was intense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAS Project - School Interior Design</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/interior-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 15:11:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/interior-design/</guid>
      <description>My imagination is more vivid than life.
50 cent Project outline Category Description Project title School Interior Design Project leader Cecilia Ontañón Berganza Members Cecilia Ontañón Berganza, Jagoda Lipowicz, Mateusz Konat, Jan Babiarz, Amelia Kamińska Focus of the project The decoration of the school building for various occasions Supervisor Aleksandra Sobala-Woźniak Anticipated dates Throught the 2022-2023 school year IPARD Investigation September 2023 There was a widespread complain about the school building&amp;rsquo;s design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Has Just Come Back!</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/start-podcast-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 07:48:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/posts/start-podcast-project/</guid>
      <description>Intro Brief info Welcome in another episode!
We haven&amp;rsquo;t talked for a while, but we&amp;rsquo;re back! Today&amp;rsquo;s podcast is a mock one. We feature another co-speaker, Filip, who will stay with us. The topics covered revolve around the World Cup 2022. We talked mostly about Argentina, Messi and Maradona. We also discussed the tense atmosphere around Polish National Team. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll find something interesting!
Topics covered New co-anchor About the podcast World Cup 2022 Argentina as a winner Messi and Maradona Cultural differences and Messi&amp;rsquo;s background Controversy around Polish National Team Michniewicz and bribery The role of journalism Football and money Success and time A possible Michniewicz&amp;rsquo;s successor To sum up&amp;hellip; Closing thoughts and goodbye Podcast episode Fast goodbye You&amp;rsquo;re up to date by now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 11:38:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://undemalum.github.io/portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello World! Welcome to my website! I&amp;rsquo;m Mateusz Konat, a passionate tech tinkerer eager to share my journey with you.
Here, you&amp;rsquo;ll discover more about me and my activities, explore my blog, and dive into my projects.
Also, you can easily navigate through the content of interest on my website using the tags at the top of each page (indicated by &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; sign like &amp;ldquo;#my projects&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;#creativity&amp;rdquo;).
Now, let me tell you more about myself!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
